{
    "subject": "resource/Robert_Bontine_Cunninghame_Graham",
    "predicate": "ontology/otherParty",
    "object": "resource/National_Party_of_Scotland",
    "human_readable": "Robert Bontine Cunninghame Graham was a member of the National Party of Scotland.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9863561391830444,
            "question": "What role did Robert Bontine Cunninghame Graham play in the National Party of Scotland?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9834333658218384,
            "question": "How did Robert Bontine Cunninghame Graham's membership in the National Party of Scotland influence his other activities or pursuits?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9829665422439575,
            "question": "What was the legacy of Robert Bontine Cunninghame Graham and his involvement with the National Party of Scotland?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9796277284622192,
            "question": "Was Robert Bontine Cunninghame Graham involved in Scottish politics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9474668502807617,
            "question": "Who was Robert Bontine Cunninghame Graham?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9415417909622192,
            "question": "What political party was Robert Bontine Cunninghame Graham a member of?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9188864231109619,
            "question": "What were some of the key issues championed by the National Party of Scotland during Robert Bontine Cunninghame Graham's involvement?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.810079038143158,
            "question": "In what country was Robert Bontine Cunninghame Graham politically active?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7440822720527649,
            "question": "What was the political climate in Scotland during Robert Bontine Cunninghame Graham's time?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5509026050567627,
            "question": "Can you name any other notable figures associated with the National Party of Scotland?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Robert Bontine Cunninghame Graham was a member of the National Party of Scotland.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7914_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was the political climate in Scotland during Robert Bontine Cunninghame Graham's time?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7914_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what country was Robert Bontine Cunninghame Graham politically active?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7914_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What were some of the key issues championed by the National Party of Scotland during Robert Bontine Cunninghame Graham's involvement?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7914_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7914_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7914_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7914_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7914_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7914_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7914_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7914_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7914_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7914_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7914_83.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple. The files mention that Robert Bontine Cunninghame Graham was a founder and first president of the Scottish Labour Party, which is a forerunner to the modern Labour Party (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7914/re-ranker-msmarco/37.txt). Additionally, he is mentioned as being involved in the National Party of Scotland (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7914/re-ranker-msmarco/40.txt), which further supports this triple."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents provide information that confirms Robert Bontine Cunninghame Graham was indeed a founder and the first president of the National Party of Scotland, as mentioned in the context provided."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}